and today's installment of spring tips
和今天的 spring 技巧 分期
we're gonna go ahead and look at
我们要去看看
server-sent events service and events or
服务器发送的事件服务和事件或
SS er refers to a protocol that allows
SS er是指允许
you to do unidirectional events being
你做单向事件
pushed from a service down to a client
从服务推送到客户
typically a browser-based client a web
通常是基于浏览器的客户端
client it's a useful in that it's done
客户这是有用的，因为它完成了
over HTTP a lot of browser supported
通过HTTP支持许多浏览器
it's a useful for any kind of
这对任何类型的
unidirectional communication this is
单向通信这是
different than for example something
与某物不同
like WebSockets which requires a
例如WebSockets，它需要一个
separate protocol and awareness of that
单独的协议和对此的意识
protocol to both the client and the
客户端和客户端的协议
service I'm not saying one is better or
服务我不是说一个更好或者
you know more useful together quite the
您知道一起使用更有用
contrary they're both very useful nav
相反，它们都是非常有用的导航
they're sort of interesting use cases
他们是一些有趣的用例
one thing that's different between
一件事之间是不同的
WebSockets and service and events is
WebSockets和服务以及事件是
that WebSockets can do bi-directional
WebSockets可以双向执行
communication now you may want to use
现在您可能想使用的通信
that if you want a more a proper
如果你想要一个更合适的
multiplex communication protocol but
复用通信协议，但是
service sensitive service and events
服务敏感的服务和事件
have their uses you can use them in lots
有他们的用途，你可以大量使用
of different legacy browsers they work
可以使用的各种旧版浏览器
very well in the command line they're
他们在命令行中很好
easy to set up there HTTP so they
容易在那里建立HTTP，所以他们
require no new protocol and if you're
不需要新协议，如果您
doing anything that is intrinsically
做本质上的事情
status based or event based and you need
基于状态或事件，您需要
no replies from the client or if you
没有来自客户的答复，或者如果您
don't mind those replies coming in via
不要介意通过收到的回复
rests and SSE is just fine so imagine
休息一下，上证所就可以了，想象一下
your Twitter timeline for example or
例如，您的Twitter时间轴或
your Facebook friend graphs of status
您的Facebook朋友状态图
notifications being updated in the
通知在
browser these are ideal sort of push
浏览器是理想的选择
only kind of event updates that we can
我们唯一可以进行的事件更新
model using sfe I want to use SC in
我想在SC中使用sfe的模型
particular in this particular
特别是这个
installment of spring tips so that we
Spring 技巧的分期付款，以便我们
can compare and contrast their
可以比较和对比他们的
implementation in spring MVC proper
在Spring MVC中正确实施
versus the the implementation in spring
与春季实施
web flex the new reactive web stack
web flex新的反应式Web堆栈
instead of spring 5 to this to this
而不是 spring 5
summer so let's go ahead and build a
夏天，让我们继续前进，建立一个
regular SC application we'll use the web
常规的SC应用程序，我们将使用网络
support and when you spring integration
支持以及当您进行Spring 整合时
now again spring integration is just
现在再次 Spring Integration 只是
what we're using here to produce events
我们在这里用来产生事件的东西
we're going to model our we're going to
我们要建模我们要
you know build a service and event
你知道建立一个服务和事件
stream of files arriving in a directory
到达目录的文件流
is that all that is that all that real
就是所有那些真实的东西
world probably not but again it doesn't
世界可能没有，但再次没有
really matter what the event source is
真正重要的是事件来源是什么
in this case what we want is to have
在这种情况下，我们想要的是
something that happens asynchronously
异步发生的事情
that we can then bridge
这样我们就可以桥接
and send those and then send back to the
并将其发送，然后发送回
to the client as a service end event in
客户端作为服务结束事件
both paradigms the reactive paradigm and
两种范式都是反应范式，
the default paradigm as you'll see it's
您将看到的默认范例是
well supported in both spring MVC and in
在Spring MVC和
the rear spring web blocks but in spring
后Spring 腹板阻塞但在 Spring
MVC the the implementation feels a
MVC的实现感觉
little bit different than then the rest
与其余的有点不同
of spring and C because spring MVC is
spring和C的值，因为spring MVC是
based on the servlet API which is
基于servlet API
intrinsically blocking right where as
本质上阻止权利
sending things that may lot last a long
发送可能持续很长时间的东西
time or that may have an infinite
时间或可能无限
duration is just part and parcel of
持续时间只是其中的一部分
being reactive that's just the everyday
每天都有反应
programming model your default case is
编程模型，您的默认情况是
writing code that accommodates that
编写适合的代码
situation so it's much more natural
情况自然而然
right you're not stepping out of the
对，你没有走出
synchronous you're not stepping out of a
同步，您不会走出
particular paradigm that is the paradigm
特定范式即范式
right so let's look at the regular one
好的，让我们看一下常规的
first we're going to create a rest
首先，我们要创建一个休息
controller here and the rest controller
这里的控制器和其余的控制器
is going to have an endpoint and let's
将有一个端点，让我们
say SSE emitter okay files and what this
说SSE发射器可以的文件，这是什么
is going to be is it's going to be at a
将会是将会在
Justin a shippi endpoint with a file I'm
贾斯汀与我的文件的Shippi端点
going to map it to a name give it a
将其映射为名称给它一个
unique client name there so I'm going to
唯一的客户名称，所以我要
call it and client if we needed to later
称它为客户，如果我们以后需要的话
and the way to do this is to create an
而做到这一点的方法是创建一个
FCM inner we're gonna give it a nice
FCM内部，我们要给它一个很好的
healthy callback here in this case sixty
在这种情况下，这里的健康回调为60
times a thousand seconds or low seconds
一千秒或低秒
and we're going to store that as the
我们将其存储为
emitter in a map but we're going to use
地图中的发射器，但我们要使用
that map as a sort of staging area a
该地图作为一种过渡区域
go-between between the weboth front end
Weboth前端之间的过渡
and they event-driven
他们是事件驱动的
any synchronous spring integration based
任何基于同步Spring 的集成
back in right so ssese knew concurrent
回到正确的位置，所以塞塞知道并发
hash map okay and I'm going to say SSE
哈希图好，我要说的是SSE
thought put putting in the name as the
思想把名字放在
context with the key and putting that in
与关键的上下文，并把它放在
there and with that done somebody should
在那里，这样做的人应该
be able to call this endpoint and a
能够呼叫这个端点和
little block the client will block the
小块客户将阻止
server side will pass of a try this the
服务器端将通过尝试
this implementation yes is he supported
这个实施是的，他支持
still time served three that one's async
仍然时间服务于三个人的异步
support so this is very similar to
支持，所以这非常类似于
returning a deferred result or a future
返回延期结果或未来
or callable in spring and receipt by
或在春季可致电并由
that that work will be back rounded and
该工作将被四舍五入，
handled on the second or separate thread
在第二个或单独的线程上处理
pool which means that the fun and cool
游泳池，这意味着乐趣和酷
one that has handling HTTP requests is
可以处理HTTP请求的是
still able to carry on right you're not
仍然能够进行下去，你不是
blocking Network so now what we need to
阻止网络，所以现在我们需要
do is we need to use the spring
要做的是我们需要使用Spring
integration file inbound adapter here to
集成文件入站适配器在这里
be aware to be made aware of a changes
意识到要有所变化
in a directory and you can see that
在目录中，您可以看到
there are a lot of other supported
还有很多其他支持
modules just on my class map here but a
模块只是在我的班级地图上，但是
lot more besides in the community as
在社区中除了
well so if you understand how to make
好吧，如果你知道如何做
this code work and pretty trivial to
此代码有效，对于
swap out the inbounded after they filed
提起诉讼后换掉入境者
in that adapter for something what's
在那个适配器里是什么
your liking right so here's our
您的喜好，所以这是我们的
integration flow right if you saw our
如果您看到了我们的集成流程
video on spring integration then you
有关 Spring Integration 的视频，那么您
know that this is a pretty common
知道这很普遍
pattern reason the spring integration
模式原因Spring 整合
Java DSL and we're using the integration
Java DSL，我们正在使用集成
flows surf entry points into the DSL and
将冲浪入口点流入DSL，
in order to make this work we need to
为了使这项工作，我们需要
provide it a inbound adapter and that
提供一个入站适配器，
inbound adapter is going to point to a
入站适配器将指向一个
directory and the directory it's going
目录及其目录
to be the result of some configuration
是某些配置的结果
so we'll just give it a default value
所以我们只给它一个默认值
here we'll say that it could be any
在这里，我们会说可能是任何
property called input Deere or it'll be
称为输入Deere的属性，否则它将是
file colon forward slash four slash home
文件冒号正斜杠四斜杠回家
directory forward slash desktop for dash
目录正斜杠桌面，用于破折号
in okay so whenever there's a new file
好的，所以只要有新文件
in that directory we want sprits print
在该目录中，我们希望将其打印出来
irrigation to publish the message so I'm
灌溉来发布消息，所以我
going to say use the inbound adapter the
会说使用入站适配器
file inbound adapter pointing it to the
文件入站适配器将其指向
in directory helps to create the
在目录中有助于创建
directory if it doesn't exist and I'm
目录，如果它不存在，我是
going to create a polar and the polar is
将创建一个极地，而极地是
going to have a spec and so the spec is
将有一个规格，所以规格是
going to dictate that requests get
将决定请求得到
processed every 1000 milliseconds there
每1000毫秒处理一次
or one second and then once the message
或一秒钟，然后一次消息
comes in we're going to transform it
进来，我们要改变它
which is going to have a payload it's
这将有一个有效载荷
giving a message with a type of payload
给出带有有效载荷类型的消息
and the the paler in this case is going
而且在这种情况下更苍白
to be file so I want to take the file
成为文件，所以我想拿文件
payload which is a little expecting and
有效载荷有点期待和
call the get absolute path method on
调用获取绝对路径方法
that payload so when
该有效载荷，所以当
form it into a string and then we can
将其形成一个字符串，然后我们可以
handle that request
处理该请求
that's requests using a service activity
使用服务活动的请求
or what is called the handle method here
或这里所谓的handle方法
right so we use a new generic handler
对的，所以我们使用一个新的通用处理程序
right here and for every message that
就在这里，对于每条消息
comes in we're going to visit every
进来，我们要去拜访每一个
single record in the ssese map for each
ssese地图中的每个记录
case on SF e SF e dot 10 I'm going to
关于SF e SF e点10的案例
send the path of course this will
发送路径，这当然
require try-catch so surround that with
需要try-catch，所以用
try catch throw new run time exception e
尝试捕获抛出新的运行时异常e
and there we are that's are fairly
那就是我们相当
simple code all we can do now I think is
简单的代码，我想我们现在所能做的就是
to remove the lambda or rather to
删除lambda或更确切地说
replace the code with a lambda and that
用lambda替换代码，然后
should do it that's pretty
应该做的很漂亮
straightforward so let's go ahead and
简单明了，让我们继续前进，
see what we've got here we've got a rest
看看我们在这里得到了我们休息
control endpoint it's going to return an
控制端点，它将返回一个
SE sse emitter whenever there's a
SE sse发射器只要有
request for a different name I think
我想换一个名字
it's already there I supposed to just
它应该已经存在了
replace it and we're going to publish in
替换它，我们将在发布
a publish a message into each one of
将消息发布到每个
these entities
这些实体
whenever a file arrives via the inbound
每当文件通过入站到达
adapter okay so let's go ahead and run
适配器好吧，让我们继续运行
this and see it work all right now then
并看到它现在可以正常工作
we should be able to go to my desktop
我们应该可以转到我的桌面
directory in there we are let's go ahead
目录，我们开始吧
and start up a test here of client if
并在此处启动客户端测试
you will so on the left curl HTP logo
你会在左侧卷曲HTP徽标
localhost 8080 for slash files for slash
本地8080用于斜杠文件
spring okay so we're going to watch that
Spring 好吧，我们要看的是
directory or watch this screen you on
目录或观看此屏幕
the left and now Kristin files touch hi
左边和现在的Kristin文件都触喜
alright there's that touch low touch
好吧，那是低接触
world etc so each time we create a new
世界等等，所以每次我们创建一个新的
file in that directory that appears as
该目录中的文件显示为
an event on the left so that seems do
左边的事件，看来
working right and of course this is well
工作正常，这当然很好
supported browser so if you're using
支持的浏览器，因此，如果您使用的是
Chrome or Safari or whatever it will
Chrome或Safari或其他任何功能
it'll do the right thing there okay so
在那里会做正确的事，所以
this is the traditional way of
这是传统的方式
implementing service and events not all
并非全部实现服务和事件
that bad and against worth highlighting
不好，值得强调
that the only thing that we need to
那是我们唯一需要做的
change
更改
on the talks of other system is this bit
在其他系统上的讨论是这个位
right here the rest of the code
在这里，其余的代码
well and presumably this bit if you're
好吧，大概这是如果你
not returning a file but the the
不返回文件，但是
messaging code is indifferent to the
消息传递代码对
source of the message right of the event
事件消息权的来源
so this is the first approach is what
所以这是第一种方法是
we'll call the regular SSE approach now
我们现在称之为常规的SSE方法
let's look at the same trick the same
让我们看看相同的技巧
implementation but done in terms of the
实施，但就
reactive web flex stack okay so kill
反应式Web Flex堆栈好吗，所以杀死
Java okay and we're going to do is we're
Java没问题，我们要做的是
going to go back to Starbucks fingernail
要回到星巴克的指甲
then use spring webflix which is instead
然后使用spring webflix代替
of springing the spring spring five
弹跳Spring 五
which is two later this year so as a
今年晚些时候是两个
result the only support for it in spring
结果是春季的唯一支持
boot is in the two data snapshots and
引导位于两个数据快照中，
we're going to call this the reactive
我们将其称为反应式
sfe okay and we use reactive web and we
好的，我们使用反应式网络，我们
use spring integration again I'm going
再次使用spring集成
to hit generate and the same is true as
击中generate，这与
last time we're going to use a spring
上一次我们要用Spring
integration inbound file adapter so we
集成入站文件适配器，因此我们
need to add that to our class path lest
需要将其添加到我们的类路径中，以免
we forget
我们忘了
close that out and try some code so this
将其关闭并尝试一些代码，这样
is also a rest controller and here we're
也是 rest controller ，我们在这里
using the web support again we're going
再次使用网络支持，我们要
to say that we want to return all the
说我们要归还所有
files for a given name name and when we
给定名称的文件以及何时
return a flux of string now fluxes are
返回字符串的通量，现在通量是
the type that use interactive support
使用交互式支持的类型
instead of a spring 5 they're based on
而不是 spring 5，它们基于
their from the project's the real active
他们从项目的真正活跃
projects via pivotal reactor project
通过枢轴反应堆项目进行的项目
they describe a 0 to n valued stream of
他们描述了0到n值的流
potentially unlimited data right so they
潜在的无限数据权利，所以他们
notify you there like a completable
像完整的通知你在那里
future that is more than just one value
未来不仅仅是一个价值
right that may happen over and over and
可能一再发生的权利
over and over and over so pass the name
一遍又一遍，所以通过这个名字
variable path variable name whether and
变量路径变量名是否和
what one what we want to do is to
我们想要做的是
respond to an event happening from
响应发生的事件
spring integration so in spring negation
Spring Integration ，因此在春季否定
see use the new inbound inbound a file
请参阅使用新的入站入站文件
and the new event arise we're going to
新事件出现了，我们将要
publish that message on a channel and
在频道上发布该消息，然后
I'm going to have a we're going to have
我要有一个我们要有一个
each new client get a new subscriber to
每个新客户都有一个新订户
that channel and then we'll use that
该频道，然后我们将使用该频道
event in the message handler to then
消息处理程序中的事件
write to the to the flux right that's
写到通量是
the publisher for the flux so same basic
流量的发布者基本相同
flow for spring integration except that
Spring 集成流程，除了
instead of having a handle method we're
而不是使用handle方法
going to create multiple handle methods
要创建多个句柄方法
a publish subscribe and also let's see
发布订阅，还让我们看看
curly bracket curly bracket and put here
大括号大括号放在这里
: file colon for slash forward slash
：文件冒号为正斜杠
home desktop in and I'm going to say
家用台式机，我要说的是
files that inbound adapter is equal to
入站适配器等于的文件
in and I'm going to use auto create
在，我将使用自动创建
directory true creates the polar again
目录true再次创建极地
stick
棒
sexpot six rate equals of thousands and
sexpot六率等于数千
here we're going to send the data send
这里我们要发送数据发送
the resulting message after
产生的消息之后
transformation on a channel so let's
在频道上进行转换，让我们
transform it right so get absolute path
正确地转换它，以获得绝对路径
and then on a channel I'm going to call
然后在频道上我要打电话
this files we need to create that
这个文件，我们需要创建
channel so beam subscribe local channel
频道，所以波束订阅本地频道
files channel and when use a message
文件通道以及何时使用消息
channels DSL to create a
通道DSL创建一个
publish/subscribe channel and then use
发布/订阅频道，然后使用
that to connect you know one messaging
建立联系，您知道一条消息
event based thing to another so I'm
基于事件的东西给另一个，所以我
going to use any when Sena misses into
当Sena错过机会时将使用任何
this channel and whenever somebody makes
这个频道，无论何时有人
a request on this we're going to add a
对此的要求，我们将添加一个
new listener to that channel okay so now
该频道的新听众好吧，现在
we say flick thought create sink and the
我们说轻弹的思想会造成下沉，
sink is the thing that we're going to
下沉是我们要做的事情
write events to but we remember that you
向写事件，但我们记得您
reactive since they're active you know
反应活跃，因为他们很活跃
handling happens in a an event loop it's
处理发生在事件循环中
not happening in a separate thread pool
不在单独的线程池中发生
so we want to make sure that we use a
所以我们要确保我们使用
serialized sink because there's a
序列化接收器，因为有一个
implicitly two different things
隐含着两件事
happening here there's the events
这里发生的事情
happening from Spring innovation which
发生在春季创新中
could happen all over multiple threads
可能会发生在多个线程上
and there's the event loop happening in
而且事件循环正在发生
the reactor world so want to bridge that
反应堆世界所以想架起桥梁
with a CLS think I'm going to use that
与CLS认为我将要使用它
to create a message handler and learn a
创建一个消息处理程序并学习
cause new message handler and whenever a
导致新的消息处理程序，并且每当
message comes in will take its payload
消息进入将占用其有效负载
and cast it to a string
并将其转换为字符串
and that we're going to write that out
并且我们将把它写出来
to the seer life to sink all right like
给观察者的生活沉没
so so I'm going to say call the next
所以我要说下一个
method that is to say notify the flux
即通知通量的方法
that there's a new value by passing the
通过传递一个新的价值
publisher or the rather the payload now
发布者或现在的有效载荷
of course this could be a lambda so we
当然这可能是lambda，所以我们
can replace that with a lambda that's
可以用一个lambda代替
much easier and in fact we can just do
容易得多，实际上我们可以做到
this right becomes pretty clean as well
这个权利也变得很干净
and if we do that when I will do this as
如果我们这样做的话，我会这样做
well so now we're down to the barest of
好吧，现在我们要谈谈
code right and in fact this could be
代码正确，实际上这可能是
just a message keep it simple so we want
只是一条消息，保持简单，所以我们想要
to do now is we want to say files
现在要做的是我们要说文件
channel but subscribe Handler and that's
频道，但订阅处理程序，那是
it Lords turn that as a response now of
上议院把它作为现在的回应
course you could take care - what if we
当然您可以保重-如果我们
go strengths right what we what we could
尽力而为，尽力而为
take care and we should take care of to
保重，我们应该照顾到
disconnect this handler from the channel
将此处理程序与频道断开连接
when the handler is done so we can also
处理程序完成后，我们还可以
say handler or rather here lies but set
说经理，或更确切地说，这是谎言，但设定了
cancellation whenever though the
取消，尽管
cancellation on the stream we want to
我们要取消的流
say a Files channel but unsubscribe
说出“文件”频道但取消订阅
Hendler okay and then we subscribe it
Hendler好的，然后我们订阅它
and we return that and that will you
我们退货，那你
know spring web blocks will
知道Spring 网块会
automatically process that flux it will
自动处理该助焊剂
take that and background it in the same
把它和背景放在同一
way but this is what you do for
方式，但这就是你要做的
everything everything that is
一切都是一切
multivalued you return the flux in and
多值，您返回的通量为和
spring web block so it's really not all
Spring Web Block，所以实际上还不是全部
that different is the same paradigm
不同就是相同的范式
we're just used to thinking about it's
我们只是习惯于思考
the default approach as opposed to be a
默认方法而不是
cyclical exceptional poach okay let's go
周期性水煮好吧，走吧
ahead and run this and see what it works
继续并运行它，看看它的工作原理
now I think that's probably going to
现在我认为那可能是
fail now that I think of it because I
现在我想到它失败了，因为我
forgot to put the mime type so let's do
忘了输入mime类型，让我们开始吧
that here as well okay there we go
在这里，好吧，我们去
I'll restart
我会重启
test it we'll go ahead and curl the
测试它，我们将继续进行
endpoint HTTP localhost in 84 slash file
84斜杠文件中的端点HTTP localhost
for - Bob and here we can say touch hi
对于-鲍勃，在这里我们可以说打招呼
I think that files already there so high
我认为文件已经很高
ten there we go please 11 12 13 etcetera
十点我们去11 12 13 etcetera
right but as we do that it's updating on
是的，但是随着我们的更新
this client ID as well in both cases we
在这两种情况下，我们也都使用此客户ID
achieve the results for sending
实现发送结果
long-lived IO back to the client it's
长期存在的IO返回给客户端
being back rounded but I think you'll
回圆，但我想你会
agree that the approach using spring web
同意使用Spring Web的方法
flux feels more natural and in this case
助焊剂感觉更自然，在这种情况下
it's possible and a valuable opportunity
这是可能的，也是宝贵的机会
for us to look at how to bridge a
让我们来看看如何桥接
threading based event event-driven sort
基于线程的事件事件驱动的排序
of code with the sort of event loop
带有事件循环的代码集
based approach for the spring web book
春季网络书的基础方法
web flux project with that thanks very
网络流量项目，非常感谢
much for watching and we'll see you next
收看很多，我们下次见
time
时间